<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_id">874679711322</string>
    <string name="playLeaderboardID">CgkI2uzkt7oZEAIQAg</string>
    <string name="adUnitID">a14cb5bcb0ef2ba</string>
    <string name="app_name">Save Newton</string>
    <string name="ad_keywords">game,mobile,action,application,video,apple</string>   
    <string name="anonymousUserID">Anonymous</string>
    <string name="diagPostLocalScore_TitleTp" formatted="false">%d - Place: %d</string>
    <string name="diagInfo_Title">Instruction</string>
    <string name="diag_btnOK">OK</string>
    <string name="diag_btnSave">Save</string>
    <string name="diag_btnCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="tipNoScore">No Record</string>
    <string name="tipLoginGoogleFailed">Failed log in your Google account, check your network or Google account setting.</string>
    <string name="tipPostOnlineFail">Post online failed, maybe network timeout, please retry later.</string>
    <string name="infoGameNote1">Save Newton is a simple game but funny and make you addictive!\n\nUse your bow shoot the falling apple, to save newton from apple\'s attack! \n\nKeep on touch left side of screen to hold bow, and release arrow when lift your finger, you can slide bow up and down when you hold it. You can switch your weapon by touching the weapon select button at the right bottom corner. Touch other part of screen should lead to game pause.\n\nThere are different weapon types and tools, you can enhancement your weapon in game store using the gold coin you got from shooting apple.</string>
    <string name="infoAppleNote1">Normal apple, shoot it to earn score and gold coin.</string>
    <string name="infoAppleNote2">Golden apple, shoot it to earn score and gold coin, and you can get ammunition of strong bow.</string>
    <string name="infoAppleNote3">Green apple, shoot it to earn score and gold coin, and you can get ammunition of weak bow, score will be double when you shoot apple with weak bow.</string>
    <string name="infoAppleNote4">Gravity apple, it can make the gravity lower to let every apple fall slowly in few seconds.</string>
    <string name="infoGameNote2">Use these powers to earn highest score! Post score online to compete with other players all over the world!\n\nBe careful! DO NOT hit Newton!</string>
    <string name="tipUnlockAchievement"  formatted="false">You have unlock achievement %s. You can post it online later.</string>
    <string name="tipSubmitScoreAndAchievementOnlineFail">Submit score and achievement online failed, pelase retry later.</string>
    <string name="tipSubmitAchievementOnlineFail">Some of achievements are submit failed, pelase retry later.</string>
</resources>
